# **AKUJIOBI NELSON.C**

## nelsonakujiobi@gmail.com

Port-Harcourt, Nigeria

070 6552 6251

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a software developer with excellent communication skills, good judgement and pays attention to minutest detail. I have passion for coding and I am adept in the use of Javascript, ReactJs, nodeJs, and python. One of my goals is to work with a fast-growing start-up where I can apply my knowledge and gain more work experience while continuously developing my software engineering skill.

### **EXPERIENCE**

May 2023 -Present

#### LessonTime

Software Developer

- Developed software applications
- Worked with senior developers to build back end and front end interface
- Updated old code base to modern development standards and improve functionality

Dec 2022 -Apr 2023

## Carsverify

Software Developer

- Increased the companies productivity to 83% by integrating an online payment gateway
- Maintenance of code base and integration of newer features

Feb 2022 -Jun 2022

#### **ElitePath**

Instructor & Technical Support

- Thought HTML, CSS and basic JavaScript to trainees
- Mediator between users and company
- Attended to users technical issues
- Support business development team for their demo

## **EDUCATION**

Sept 2013 -Dec 2018 Federal University of Technology, Owerri

**Statistics** 

B.Tech

## SKILLS HOBBIES

- Software Development
- API Design Integration
- SQL integration
- Project Management

- Learning new language
- Reading
- Sleeping
- Soccer

#### **LANGUAGES**

English, Spanish(basic), Igbo